Mission Control:
\hSystems ACS 1.
We just had transition
\h\hto high rate mode.
And we are in the atmosphere.
We have loss of signal at
\h\h\h\h[unintelligible].
Project manager.
Flight director.
Go ahead.
Julie Webster: We call loss of
\h\h\h\h\hsignal at 11:55:46.
Earl Maize: This is project
\h\h\hmanager on FSO co-ord.
There may be a trickle of
\h\h\h\h\htelemetry left,
but you just heard the signal
\hfrom the spacecraft is gone
and, in the next 45 seconds, so
will be the spacecraft.
I hope you’re all
\has deeply proud
of this amazing accomplishment.
Congratulations to you all!
\h\hThis has been an
incredible mission,
an incredible spacecraft,
and you’re all an
\hincredible team!
I’m going to call this
\hthe end of mission.
Project manager off the net.
[applause]
NASA Jet Propulsion Laboratory
California Institute of
\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTechnology